{
    "id": "4445d65d2f4f4ea4b8ee54c05f22883d",
    "title": "Possessive Pronouns And Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She claimed that the money was ............................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec5fdacf66424f8fbbea90ef498a8b5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some students have left ................................ notebooks in the class.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "271336c35171446f80314ebde176e36f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never been to ............................... home.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10487e99e6504bb1ae4b5c171095ae72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Sam nor Peter can remember ............................ passwords.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9854bfdb9f0841c4b2298ab54f06fba7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She told me that the bag was ................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "728c4a67ee22469aa3887840d530899a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been to their home several times but they have never been to ..................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa1ec59b39ef4273ae9a88bb826d5ba6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She found .............................. passport but we couldn't find ...............................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her, our",
                "hers, ours",
                "her, ours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5d1c7895a38c4638adb1721740141648"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a lot of friends but none of them was invited for ........................... birthday.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0db4de7fbc444f4e9ef6c936ef61f7e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think this pen is ................................",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "436c2cf38f4c406f91ac9587cd8ec64f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him if he had seen ............................. key.",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "255072ef81eb4e378624e547ba704c14"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked him what he was doing in ............................. room",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0128244d838b4cdb81c8903005490114"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can show you my ID. Can I see ................................?",
            "description": "The words my, his, her, their, our and your are possessive adjectives. Use them before a noun. The words mine, his, hers, theirs, ours and yours are possessive pronouns. Use them alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5576d8274b554d878efeaa872d4c8b09"
        }
    ]
}